# **ADRIA LWIN**

778-889-1459 adrialwin@gmail.com <u>Website</u> <u>GitHub</u> Vancouver, BC

#### SUMMARY

I am a recent UBC graduate with a life sciences degree and a keen interest in computer science and building cool things. I have several years of experience in the medical administrative field but I'm very excited to pursue a new career in the tech industry. Some areas that interest me are backend and frontend development, database management and eCommerce.

#### EDUCATION AND CERTIFICATES

# **University of British Columbia**

2014 - 2020

Bachelor of Science, Combined Major in Science

Relevant Coursework: Software Construction, Algorithms and Data Structures

# University of Michigan, Coursera

2022

Python for Everybody Specialization

Highlighted Coursework: Data Structures, Accessing Web Data, Using Databases

## WORK EXPERIENCE

Medical Office Assistant, Dr. T. Alan Demco Ophthalmologist

Dec 2018 - Present

- Multitask by troubleshooting technical problems while answering 100+ calls and emails daily
- Onboarded >10 new employees and served as first contact for hundreds of new patients
- Draft written communications to other doctors and legal offices

## Seasonal Concierge Advisor, Aritzia

Oct 2021 - Feb 2022

- Achieved top daily department-wide sales on multiple occasions
- Reached company quotas of 5.5 interactions per hour with a 5/5 client satisfaction rating
- Provided tailored support via live-chat, phone and email channels

#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

Chinese Checkers Mar 2022

- Developed Chinese checkers console app in Java
- Used recursion to model gameplay on a 2D array representation of a star-shaped board
   Relevant skills: Java, JUnit, Git, Github, Markdown, Command line, VSCode

<u>www.adrialwin.com</u>
May 2022

- Built a responsive personal website and hosted it using Heroku
- Prototyped desktop and mobile designs using Figma
   Relevant skills: Heroku, Figma, HTML, CSS, Media queries, Bootstrap, Rails

## **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

#### President, Amnesty International UBC

Apr 2018 - May 2020

- Organized events and annual conference to bring attention to critical human rights violations, often in collaboration with other university clubs
- Lead weekly meetings to set goals and assign responsibilities